Guide to the News Service subject files, 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Students, General, 1988 (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1990 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1991 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1995 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1996 (Box 75)
  - Prospective Students, 1975-1977 (Box 76)
  - Prospective Students, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Student Symposium (Box 76)
  - Duke Student Government, 1993 (Box 76)
  - Students Honors and Awards, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Student Legislature, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Student Organizations, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Students, Political, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Students, Political, 1996 (Box 76)
  - Study Abroad, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Study Abroad, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Study Abroad, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Summer Arts Program, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Summer Enrichment Program (Box 76)
  - Summer Entertainment Program, 1970 (Box 76)
  - Summer Programs, 1987 (Box 76)
  - Summer Programs, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Summer Programs, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Summer Programs, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Summer Programs, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Summer Science and Math Institute, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Summer Session, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Summer Session, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
  - Summer Theatre (Box 76)
  - Super Collider, 1987-1988 (Box 76)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general,1977-1981 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1983 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1984 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1986 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1987 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Symposia general, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Tel-Com (Box 76)
  - Tel-Com, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1976-1981 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences, 1982 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences, 1984 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences, 1986 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1992 (Box 76)
  - Terry Sanford Institute of Public Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 76)
  - Terry Sanford Institute of Public Policy, 1995 (Box 76)
  - Governor's Center (Box 76)
  - Governor's Center, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Governor's Center, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
  - Governor's Center, 1991 (Box 76)
  - TIP, 1981 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1982 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1983 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1984 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1985 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1986 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1987 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1988 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1989 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1990 (Box 77)
  - TIP, 1991 (Box 77)
  - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 77)
  - Triangle Universities Computation Center, 1975 (Box 77)
  - Triangle Universities Nuclear Lab TUNL, 1975 (Box 77)
  - Triangle Universities Nuclear Lab TUNL, 1985 (Box 77)
  - Trinity College (Box 77)
  - Trinity Forerunners before 1892 (Box 77)
  - Trinity Forerunners, 1989 (Box 77)
  - Tropical Studies, Organization for, 1989-1990 (Box 77)
  - Technology and the Liberal Arts, 1985 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1968 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1978-1985 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1987 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1988 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1989 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1990 (Box 78)
  - Theatre, 1991 (Box 78)
  - Thelonious Monk Institute (Box 78)
  - Thelonious Monk Institute, 1989 (Box 78)
  - Thelonious Monk Institute, 1990 (Box 78)
  - Trustees, 1966 (Box 78)
  - Trustees, 1970-1972 (Box 78)
  - Trustees, 1975 (Box 78)
  - Tuition, 1983-1985 (Box 78)
  - Tuition, 1987 (Box 78)
  - Tuition, 1988 (Box 78)
  - Tuition, 1989 (Box 78)
  - Tuition, 1990 (Box 78)
  - Bryan Center, Student Union (Box 78)
  - United Way Fund, 1975 (Box 78)
  - United Way Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 78)
  - Visiting Journalists (Box 78)
  - Visiting Journalists, 1988 (Box 78)
  - Visiting Journalists, 1989-1990 (Box 78)
  - Queen of Jordan's Visit, April 1985 (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Visiting Professors, 1975 (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Visitors, 1977 (Box 79)
  - Visiting Professors, 1987 (Box 79)
  - Visiting Professors, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Visiting Professors, 1989-1990 (Box 79)
  - Visiting Professors, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Volunteers, 1990 (Box 79)
  - Volunteers includes Community Service Center, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Volunteers, 1992 (Box 79)
  - Whitehead Institute (Box 79)
  - Duke Wind Symphony (Box 79)
  - Wind Symphony, 1987 (Box 79)
  - Wind Symphony, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Winterfest (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies Center, 1981 (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies Center, 1987 (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies Center, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies and Women's Center, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies and Women's Center, 1990 (Box 79)
  - Women's Studies Program and Women's Center, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Workshops-Miscellaneous (Box 79)
  - Workshops-Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Workshops-Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 79)
  - Writer's Conference, 1985 (Box 79)
  - Zoology (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1979 (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1985 (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1986 (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Zoology, 1989-1990 (Box 79)
  - Academics, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Academic Council, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Academic Council, 1988 (Box 80)
  - Academic Council, 1989 (Box 80)
  - Academic Council, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Academic Skills Program, 1988 (Box 80)
  - Academic Skills Program, 1989 (Box 80)
  - Accounting (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1977-1979 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1978-1981 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1982 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1984 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1987 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1988 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1989 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1992 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1993 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1994 (Box 80)
  - African-American Studies, 1993 (Box 80)
  - African-American Studies, 1994 (Box 80)
  - Aging, 1992 (Box 80)
  - Alumni general, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Alumni general, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Alumni general, 1993 (Box 80)
  - Alumni Affairs/Alumni Association, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1994 (Box 80)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1996 (Box 80)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1997 (Box 80)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1998 (Box 80)
  - ASDU Associated Students of Duke University, 1977-1985 (Box 81)
  - ASDU, 1988 (Box 81)
  - ASDU, 1989-1990 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1990 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1991 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1992 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1993 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1994 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1996 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1997 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1998 (Box 81)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1999 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Athletics, 1975 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1977-1979 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1979 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1980 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1981 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1981 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1982 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1983 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Athletics, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1977-1981 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1982-1986 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1990 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1991 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1992 (Box 84)
  - Awards, 1993 (Box 84)
  - Band, 1978 (Box 84)
  - Band, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Band, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Band, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Biddle Foundation, 1977-1986 (Box 84)
  - Biochemistry, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Biology, 1982-1985 (Box 84)
  - Biology, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Biology, 1991- (Box 84)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy, 1993 (Box 85)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1975 (Box 85)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Black Studies (Box 85)
  - Black Studies, 1977-1983 (Box 85)
  - Black Studies, 1989-1995 (Box 85)
  - Black Studies, 1991 (Box 85)
  - David Peter Bloom, 1988-1989 (Box 85)
  - Botany, 1976-1986 (Box 85)
  - Botany, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
  - Botany, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Brit/Am Fest, Pictures and Bios (Box 85)
  - British-American Festival (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1990 (Box 85)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1978 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1979 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1981 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1982 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1983 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1985 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1986 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1987 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Bryan Center, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, Financial Reports (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1978 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1979 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1981 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1986 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1987 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1990 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Budget and Finance, 1993 (Box 85)
  - Buildings, 1977-1978 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1979 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1980 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1983 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1984-1985 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1986 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1987 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1989 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1990 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1992 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1993 (Box 86)
  - Buildings, 1994 (Box 86)
  - Music Building (Box 86)
  - Medical Center Complex (Box 86)
  - Library Interior (Box 86)
  - Dormitories Undergraduate Men (Box 86)
  - Chemistry Building (Box 86)
  - Master Campus Plan (Box 86)
  - Swimming Pool (Box 86)
  - Service Center (Box 86)
  - Cable 13, 1982-1986 (Box 86)
  - Cable 13, 1989-1990 (Box 86)
  - Campaign for Duke, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Campaign for Duke, 1989 (Box 86)
  - Campaign for Duke, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Campus Club, 1978-1986 (Box 86)
  - Campus Community Council, 1971 (Box 86)
  - Campus Ministry, 1989-1990 (Box 86)
  - Canadian Studies Center, 1976-1985 (Box 86)
  - Canadian Studies, 1989 (Box 86)
  - Canadian Studies, 1990 (Box 86)
  - Canadian Studies, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1987 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1990 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Capital Campaign, 1992 (Box 86)
  - Duke Card (Box 86)
  - Career Development Center, 1989-1990 (Box 86)
  - Career Development Center, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Career Development Center, 1992 (Box 86)
  - Career Development Center, 1993 (Box 86)
  - Center for Demographic Studies, 1975 (Box 87)
  - Center for Demographic Studies, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Center for Demographic Studies, 1989- (Box 87)
  - Center for Demographic Studies, 1993 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Photography (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Photography, 1987 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Photography, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1991 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1992 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1993 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1994 (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 87)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 87)
  - Center for East-West Trade, Investments, and Communications, 1992-1993 (Box 87)
  - Center for Health Policy and Research (Box 87)
  - Center for Health Policy Research and Education, 1985 (Box 87)
  - Center for Health Policy and Research, 1989-1990 (Box 87)
  - Center for International Development and Research, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Center for International Studies (Box 87)
  - Center for Slavic, Eurasian, and Eastern European Studies, 1992-1994 (Box 87)
  - Center for Southern Studies, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Center for Study of Aging and Human Development, 1993 (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, 1994-1996 (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of Communications and Journalism (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of Communications Policy, 1982 (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of the Family and the State, 1977 (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of Governorship and State Policy Making, 1980 (Box 87)
  - Center for the Study of Philanthropy and Volunteerism, 1989-1990 (Box 87)
  - Center for VSSR Manager Development, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Center for VSSR Manager Development, 1991 (Box 87)
  - Center for World Environment and Sustainable Development, 1991 (Box 87)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1970 (Box 87)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1989 (Box 87)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1991 (Box 87)
  - Doubletake, 1995 (Box 87)
  - Duke Chapel, 1977 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1978 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1979-1980 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1981 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1981-1985 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1982 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1983 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1985 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1986 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1987 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1989 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1990 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1991 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1992 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1994 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1996 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, 1997 (Box 88)
  - Duke Chapel, Photographs (Box 88)
  - Chemistry, 1975-1983 (Box 88)
  - Chemistry, 1989-1990 (Box 88)
  - Chemistry, 1991 (Box 88)
  - Chemistry, 1993 (Box 88)
  - Children's Classic, 1987 (Box 88)
  - Children's Classic, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Children's Classic, 1989 (Box 88)
  - Children's Classic, 1990 (Box 88)
  - Children's Classic, 1991 (Box 88)
  - Chorale Activities, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Chorale Activities, 1987 (Box 88)
  - Chorale Activities, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Chorale Activities, 1989-1990 (Box 88)
  - Chorale Activities, 1991 (Box 88)
  - Chronicle (Box 88)
  - Chronicle, 1971-1973 (Box 88)
  - Chronicle, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Chronicle, 1990 (Box 89)
  - Chronicle, 1991 (Box 89)
  - Chronicle, 1993 (Box 89)
  - Chronicle, 1994-1998 (Box 89)
  - Church Related Activities (Box 89)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1988 (Box 89)
  - Classical Studies Department (Box 89)
  - Classical Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 89)
  - Collegium Musicum, 1985 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1980 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1981 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1982 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1983 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1985 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1986 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1987 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1988 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1990 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 19991 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1992 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1993 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1994 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1995 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1995 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1996 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1996 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1997 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1997 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1998 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1998 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1999 (Box 89)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1999 (Box 89)
  - Commencement, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Commencement, 1982-1985 (Box 90)
  - Computer Camp, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Computer Science, 1977-1988 (Box 90)
  - Computer Science, 1989-1990 (Box 90)
  - Computer Science, 1991 (Box 90)
  - Computer Science, 1992 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1977 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1982 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1983 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1985 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1986 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1987 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Concerts and Plays, 1990 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1985 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1986 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1987 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1988 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1990 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1991 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1993 (Box 90)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1997-1998 (Box 90)
  - Continuing Education, 1975-1984 (Box 91)
  - Contnuing Education, 1980 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1981 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1984 (Box 91)
  - Credit Union, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
  - Credit Union, 1988 (Box 91)
  - Counseling and Psychological Serv, 1989-90 CAPS (Box 91)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services CAPS, 1980- (Box 91)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services, 1988 (Box 91)
  - Credit Union, 1969 (Box 91)
  - Convocation, 1985 (Box 91)
  - Convocation and Pastor's School, 1987- (Box 91)
  - Convocation and N.C. Pastor's School, 1977-1986 (Box 91)
  - Corporate Executives Conference, October 1977 (Box 91)
  - Craft Center (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1986 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1979 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1976 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1977 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1985 (Box 91)
  - Productivity Conference, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing Symposium 1980 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1991- (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1990 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1989 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1988 (Box 91)
  - Continuing Education, 1987 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars: "Substance Abuse in the Workplace- Strategies for the 1990's" (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1977 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1978 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1979 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1980 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1981 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Day Care Center, 1972 (Box 92)
  - Day Care Center, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Day Care Center, 1989 (Box 92)
  - Day Care Center, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Dean's List, 1989-90 (Box 92)
  - Dean's List, 1975 (Box 92)
  - Dean's List, 1979-1982 (Box 92)
  - Dean's List, 1975-1978 (Box 92)
  - Dean's List, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Debating Team, 1977 (Box 92)
  - Development (Box 92)
  - Development, 1994-1996 (Box 92)
  - Development, 1992 (Box 92)
  - Development, 1981 (Box 92)
  - Development, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Development, 1989-90 (Box 92)
  - Development, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Curriculum, 1991-1996 (Box 92)
  - Curriculum, 1989-90 (Box 92)
  - Curriculum, 1975 (Box 92)
  - Curriculum, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1992 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Duke Dance Program, 1977 (Box 92)
  - Dance general, 1977-1982 (Box 92)
  - Duke Dance Program, 1983 (Box 92)
  - Duke Dance Program, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1987 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1989 (Box 92)
  - Dance Program, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Anthropology, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Anthropology, 1993 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Anthropology, 1994 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1987 (Box 92)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1991-1993 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1979-1986 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1989 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1987 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Crime, 1991 (Box 92)
  - The Devil energy efficient car, 1979 (Box 92)
  - Dining Halls, 1975 (Box 92)
  - Dining Halls, 1988 (Box 92)
  - Dining Halls, 1992-1993 (Box 92)
  - Dining Halls, 1989 (Box 92)
  - Dining Halls, 1990- (Box 92)
  - Divinity School, 1986 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1981 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1982 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1983 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1984 (Box 93)
  - Divinity School, 1985 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1992 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1991 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1975 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1989-1990 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1991 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1991 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1984 Duke's Trinity College of Arts and Sciences (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1999 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Divinity, 1993 (Box 93)
  - J. M. Ormond Center for Research, Planning, and Development Divinity School, 1972 (Box 93)
  - DoubleTake, 1997-2000 (Box 93)
  - Drugs and Alcohol, 1997-1998 (Box 94)
  - Drugs and Alcohol,1995-1996 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Abuse, Prevention, 1991 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Abuse, Prevention, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Drug Abuse Prevention, etc., 1972 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Abuse, Prevention, 1987 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Abuse, Prevention, 1988 (Box 94)
  - Drugs Abuse, Prevention, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program- General Information (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1978-1986 (Box 94)
  - Equity Theater (Box 94)
  - "Circle Theater" (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1993 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1992 (Box 94)
  - Lucifer's Child, 1990-1991 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1989 (Box 94)
  - "Metamorphosis," 1988-1989 (Box 94)
  - "Moonlight and Valentino" (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1977 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1978 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1981 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1982 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1983 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1984 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1985 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1986 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1988 (Box 94)
  - Duke Players, 1987 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1996 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1996 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1977 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1978 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1981 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1982 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1983 (Box 94)
  - A Month of Sundays (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1993-1994 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1986 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Drama Program, 1991 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1988 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1987 (Box 94)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Duke/Durham, 1994 (Box 95)
  - Duke/Durham, 1995 (Box 95)
  - Duke/Durham, 1996 (Box 95)